So friends, in this video we
will discuss about Alok Industries and the
questions that you have about many cities
and the tension that is happening on the India-China border, will it have
any impact on the market, we
will discuss all these things in more detail and welcome to your own
channel TK Money, my name is Tribhuvan
Should Fight in Equity Derivatives
Unauthorized, there is a question that many people have
here since yesterday that the
Jio political tensions that are going on on the India-China border, will it have a
negative impact on the market, the stock market, remember the
market will crash, the market will get mixed
if something happens, there is one thing I will tell you, if you
look at the historical data,
go into history and see the market value, the
problem has been solved through normal talks,
now the market is not going to give any big reaction,
but if let's assume that no solution is found to this problem
and a
little more controversy is increased here, then
in that situation there can definitely be a correction in the market, so
if you go into history and
see, the market will end up 12%
Whenever there has been any geopolitical tension, the
market can do this because of that, that is, there can be a
fall, there can be profit
booking, it can also happen because many
people had banked on the lower levels
and are in a lot of profit, if
some negative news starts coming then there can be a fall, the
second thing is that the market
never moves only by looking at the market of its own country, you know I had
also discussed once that the market should
also wash away the global market, elections are going to be held in America now
and we have to see what the result can be,
Donald Trump is going to win, it can be like this, the
market can
show correction, it can be the
market of America, the market is very
smart, it can
show correction before the result, so if this
market corrects here, then the whole market of the world will
connect, India's market will also do it,
so the market moves by looking at many things,
it moves by looking at its funda minutes,
it moves by looking at the national market, what is the
protein trend tomorrow,
where is the market here  But look, if
this problem continues, there is
not such a big need right now, but if the
confidence here increases, then some correction can definitely happen.
Pay some attention to things
and trade accordingly. Be a
little worried while trading. The
market is showing turmoil. Do
not invest all at once, do
systematic investment, do some
measurement. Their mother friend
is also not appointed at 8000 that cash withdrawal will only go up. The
appointment right now is that you have to take good
stocks in your portfolio stocks
and invest only a little Jai Limited. Do
not invest too much because the market
can show correction here. But
if this is resolved, then the market can
also rally again. Pay attention to this. So,
you should think carefully and go through the columns here on
Infratel. This question of sir is good. Let me
tell you that the stock of Infratel, in some
way, it is the
staff and applicant of Idea. In first
and technically and fundamentally, it is a
strong company.  I have
Infratel Vostok, which I have been
driving before, during this medical, 34 percent during this period
and
I don't know what they found this year, but it was up by 3-4
percent at that time also, but it is a
company that offers a different style, Idea is a good company,
if you look at the competition, but today the
fall in Idea is because of
infertility, Idea and these World
Bank
relations, but there is a rise, there is a rise
in these protests also, even if the rise is less,
and if Idea falls then they are
arrested, you know that what we
said about Idea that it is not for weak people,
that is to say that in a big situation, those
people can take a lot of risk,
well for Hui, you can see that it fell by 8 percent in one day,
if it continues like this, there is 20 percent
up, 8-10 percent down in a day,
this kind of volatility, its
internal alert is very high, there is a lot of aircraft, a
lot of what is
in talks, I say that only those traders should work
or those who work in investors, they can
take more risk if the investment is
right.  If this happens then this Idea
stock can run, it can run quite well.
There is a risk here also that you have
uncertainty here, you do
n't know what will happen. Well, secondly, let me talk about Honey Colgate, it
is an amazing company, technically it is good,
fundamentally it is a very good source, there is no
shortage in it, the
company generates free stro, if you look at it, the
difference and demerits of the
three percent is around 2.5 percent,
you don't have to worry about the management quality,
these types of companies are
very old companies, they have a lot of hold
in the market, let me tell you one thing, this is the
stock of the school portfolio, you can just take
it down by 15-20% whenever it falls from its old swing,
okay now let's talk about levels,
but for Russia, you will have to go
to the Telegram channel,
go to Telegram and search for
PK Money, you will search for TK Company, the
channel will come up, come on, there is a lot of
additional CMHO, he discusses  That no one
ever gives us any tips because I do
n't trust tips at all,
they don't work in the market, the market
works on your fundamental and technical knowledge, I share my data from here
or if you see investment options,
share them or if there is some
educational post, I share it with you guys,
so you can go to TK Manisha
sir, you will get it
on Telegram, there it is
easy to tell the labels, you can update the life market,
which is not possible on YouTube,
this Colgate is a good stock and I
think the price has been given technically, after
seeing that I will discuss with you guys on Telegram as well,
so Colgate, you know, is a
portfolio stock, by John Adams'
friend at edition print, if I
tell you about it, it is very good, technically it is also
very good fundamentally, but will you
take it sir, I will say I will
not take it at all, the
first street is also good fundamentally, I
also do not want to take it on the website, why
not stay, the sacrifice is very important  No matter
how good a product is,
if you get it at a very high rate, the
profit potential reduces. So,
you have to pay attention. You have to keep Asian Paints
on your watch list. You have to keep it on your watch list. You have to
enter when the market falls or Asian Paints goes grey. You have to enter now. You do
n't have to rush right now. It is a leader in its segment and
around Diwali, Husain's price also increases.
Cummins is a thing, but I
always tell you this about the train. When the train starts moving,
friend, if you mix it up, please do
n't run to catch it,
otherwise it can be a big problem. Let it
stop once, let it come to the right price.
There, again, it can be
admitted for flowers. Gradually,
I am talking about investors.
Look at the trading, the labels are taken out and seen.
You need to do it on the Telegram service
here and do a proper daily
massage. Well, let me tell you one thing
about Alok Industries. Today,
again, Alok Industries' stock
closed in the negative. The stock of Maa also
closed in the negative. Well, the potato is in the
market, it definitely showed a jump, but here
As the salary has come and you can see
that there is a lot of problem on the top, the
support is still working here,
you know the support is there, the 25th of
June is the support area, it was the
resistance area of ​​14.5, there was
talk of profit booking in the jam and many people took
profit, there was also talk of correction there,
now the area of ​​this award is the area of
25, the area of ​​2530, so we are
expecting to take support from here,
even today you can see in Android, it has
definitely come around 28 twice, that employment has gone down by three and a half percent, more than that
you know that you are rolling on the difference of half an hour,
this last candle is shown,
you cannot take the risk by looking at it, keep this thing in mind,
with sending a lot of
results, has anyone come,
let's see something on the NSE-BSE side, do
n't tell me what kind of news has
come that potato hour after this  The results are
coming at this time, so there
is no discussion about any pimp yet. Well, it is
scattered around a very important mill.
If you put some long-term charts on the site,
monthly charts, then it is
coming around an important level and there is definitely hope for a boom here,
but here it is important to pay attention
that if the overall market starts correcting, then there
can be a problem, that market
correction starts, then
friends, from this grip, nothing is
seen, this is the market current, so
wherever there is profit, they take those whose
bottom will be taken, pay attention to this, but
if you have
always seen them, then
here we have to pay attention to one thing, the
price section and the volume, the
biggest candle of volume, you know, I
discussed this earlier also, is this candle or not, this
area which you are seeing is very clear
around 26 and this is 2030, if you simply do it, the
Reserve Bank of India libas
phone of 2530, this is an important zone, from here it
is expected that there will be a reversal.  It should come and if someone else
gets it then there can be a reversal. Pay
attention to this thing that even if there is a reversal here, I
think it will go till 3536.
In the first round, we will
see the film price section there and will update it.
But the first reversal that should come should
come from support because everyone did
not stop voting. So what happens then, you have
seen in Bharti Airtel, I had
also updated you guys
about Bharti Airtel's pollution, so you
can see it here. So the next stock is
IS A Long Gap, a very high quality company. It is
technically a very good stock in the general insurance space. In my opinion, the
IPO which came was around 1622
and it says because it had also come down from there, you
can also go and see it on the chart from 800 to 1000 and it had come down from there, it is also
down, so it did not even become Ras Malai,
I remember it, but it doubled from there. Today,
he trusted him, due to which people came on board.
Salman doubled it directly and gave him profit.
Fundamentally, it is a very good company.  The
insurance space, you know
what's happening in the sector, there's significant
growth visible. There's a good company here,
it's a flower stock, a lot of investors have bought and
kept it. It's a favorite of f5. It's one of the favorite stocks of
foreign institutional investors.
But pay a little attention. If
you're right-
priced, it would be better.
Here I
have 12.50, I'll have to set up fiber support registration once.
If you
get option D there, you can enter it.
Pay a little attention.
Now, the next stock, let's say Apollo Hospital, has taken a look at the fundamentals of Apollo
Hospital. There's no
shortage in it.
This is also a Bryan Adams candidate. But
I've noticed one thing: if the business
tone is a little low, Apollo Hospital
also falls by 40 degrees. I've seen it from the top. Be a
little cautious. So
far, there's no shortage
in Apollo Hospital. But the rest of the levels, we'll
discuss them on Telegram.
You can also call Apollo Hospital a flavor stock.  There are flowers and fennel, it is a good
stock, there is no shortage in it, it is number six from I,
it is a very high quality stock, there is no
shortage in it, just work a little by looking at the levels,
you will get to know
how the technical fundamentalists are, then you should
look at the labels, friends, this video is here, now let's
roast it
and you know that disclaimer is a DJ video,
it has been made for educational information,
so please like your video,
contact us, any decision has to be taken, there are
many types of risks in the market, thank you.